faster-pc.net 2016-11-01

# Faster-PC.net Privacy Policy

## This privacy policy applies to the use of Faster-PC.net.

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site. 

## Log Files and Cookies

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally indentifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site. 

## Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

## Registration and Use of Personal Information

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. 

We also provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. In this case, we ask the visitor for his or her email address and name. These communications will include our regular newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email we send to you.

Again, if you provide us with your email address and/or name for the purposes of receiving communications from us, this information will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

## Security

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore – as is the case with any organization - we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information. 

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by using the contact form.

## Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

## Contact Details

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us for any other reason, please use the contact form.

## How to uninstall software you have downloaded from this site

Faster-PC.net only recommends software that we believe is helpful to your computer and easy to use. The simplicity of the uninstallation process is part of the criteria we use to evaluate software programs that are linked to from this site.

To uninstall any software you download from this site, please take the following steps:

  * Open your Start menu and click the "Control Panel" button
  * Open the "Add/Remove Programs" icon (or "Programs and Features" on Vista and Windows 7)
  * You will now see a list of all the software installed on your computer. Find the program you wish to uninstall and click it once to select it.
  * Press "Uninstall", and follow the on-screen directions.

The software should now be removed from your computer. 

This privacy policy was last updated on December 19, 2009.
